Guide to the New York Metro Area Postal Union Photographs PHOTOS.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
New York Metro Area Postal Union Photographs
circa 1955-1981
PHOTOS.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
5.0 linear feet in three record cartons, one manuscript box, and one oversize flat box.
This collection contains the photographs of the New York Metro Area Postal Union, the New York City local branch of the American Postal Workers Union. The collection contains circa 2500 images of individuals, events, strikes, committee meetings, and other proceedings that document the history of the local, the bulk are from the 1950s to 1980.
New York Metro Area Postal Union.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The New York Metro Area Postal Union (American Postal Workers Union, Local 10) represents clerks, motor vehicle staff, maintenance workers and mail-handlers in the greater New York City area. (Some mail-handlers, however, are represented by other unions.) By the 1980s the union enrolled more than 25,000 members. The local originated as Local 10 of the National Federation of Post Office Clerks. Officers and most of the members of this local seceded in 1958 to become the Postal Union of Manhattan-Bronx Clerks (which in 1960 changed its name to the Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union), with the aim of uniting many postal craft workers into one industrial union. The union became part of the newly-created American Postal Workers Union in 1971, after taking a leading role in the hard-fought national strike of postal workers in 1970. Under the presidencies of Moe Biller and Josie MacMillan from the 1958 through the 1980s, the local union won significant gains for its members. Both the membership and the leadership became more diverse as post office jobs opened up to minorities and women as a result of civil rights initiatives in the 1960s. In 1973 the union changed its name to the New York Metro Area Postal Union, the new name reflecting the inclusion of the New York Bulk and Foreign Mail Center and the North Jersey Facility in the local's bargaining unit.
Scope and Content Note
This collection of approximately 2500 photographs (many are copy prints for the Union's publication, The Union Mail) documents the concerns of the New York Metro Area Postal Union's membership over a twenty-five year period (1955-1981). Images of rallies and demonstrations show the issues around which the union organized and the changing language for those demands. Of special interest are the shots of the union's delegation leaving for the 1963 March on Washington. In addition, the collection also includes photoprints of individuals, bargaining sessions, and national conventions. There are some images of union-sponsored social groups, such as the chess club and bowling team. The union's lobbying is reflected in images of local and national union leadership with various politicians including John F. Kennedy, Robert F. ("Bobby") Kennedy, Kenneth Keating, and Congressman John Lindsay. The collection also contains a significant number of negatives.
The original folder titles for the photographs as received from the union have largely been retained, but the information in them, and on the backs of many of the photographs as well, is not always accurate.
Related Archival Materials
American Postal Workers Union: Moe Biller Files (WAG 099)
American Postal Workers Union Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 026)
New York Metro Area Postal Union Records (WAG 103)
New York Metro Area Postal Union Oral History (OH 003)
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into twenty-eight series.
Series I: Individuals
Series II: Group Portraits with Union Officials
Series III: Congressional Visits
Series IV: Meetings
Series V: Stewards
Series VI: Group Portraits of Union Officials at Events
Series VII: House/Senate Members Visit the Union
Series VIII: Membership Meetings
Series IX: Delegates
Series X: Installation of Officers
Series XI: Conventions/Conferences
Series XII: Boards/Committees/Councils
Series XIII: Women's Auxiliary
Series XIV: Demonstrations/Rallies
Series XV: Signs/Billboards
Series XVI: Elections
Series XVII: Contracts
Series XVIII: Dinners/Parties
Series XIX: Award Ceremonies
Series XX: Classes/Seminars
Series XXI: Workplaces
Series XXII: Union Office Staff
Series XXIII: The Union Mail
Series XXIV: Sports/Recreation
Subseries A: Baseball
Subseries B: Softball
Subseries C: Basketball
Subseries D: Bowling
Subseries E: Chess
Subseries F: Handball
Subseries G: Miscellaneous
Series XXV: National Federation of Postal Clerks, Local 10 (New York)
Series XXVI: Miscellaneous
Series XXVII: Addendum
Series XXVIII: Negatives
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Photographs in this collection were separated from the New York Metro Area Postal Union Records (WAG 103). Between late 1980 and early 1981 photographs in this collection was donated by the New York Metro Area Postal Union via Bernard Schwartz, a representative to the American Postal Workers Union. The accession number associated with these materials is 1970.020. In 1996, a small portion of photographs were removed from the New York Metro Area Postal Union’s organizational records (WAG 103) and added to the photographs collection. The accession number associated with these materials is NPA.1996.003.
Biller, Moe, 1915-2003; MacMillan, Josie; Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union.; National Federation of Post Office Clerks. Local 10 (New York, N.Y.).; Postal Union of Manhattan-Bronx Clerks.; United States Postal Service.; Photographs.; Postal service |x Employees |x Labor unions |z United States.; Postal service |x Employees |x Labor unions.; Postal Strike, U.S., 1970.
- Series I: Individuals, A (Box 1)
  Scope and Content Note
  Not all of the images in this series are formal portraits; many are them are photographs in which the named person is the only person in the photograph,or where most of the pictures focus on the person named.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Aarons, Roy, undated
  - Abbott, John, 1959
  - Anthony, Ms. J. Raffle w/ S. Goodman., undated
  - Auchinclass, Rep. J.C. (1 portrait), undated
  - Aufiero, M.D. Members speak., 1960
  - Aurutin, H.-Central Trades Union Chairman, undated
  - Barone, Joseph. Members speak., Mar 1966
  - Biaggi, Rep. M., 1960
  - Biller, Moe, undated
  - Biller, Moe, Mar 1967
  - Blacksin, H.- VP, undated
  - Bowley, Ed- National Legislative Chairman NPU, Aug 1969
  - Boyd, William- General Post Office Trans., Nov 1968
  - Brown, Carl- VP, Morgan Station, 1959
  - Cannon Marion- VP, General Post Office, undated
  - Chase, Clifford P.- Senator, NJ (1 portrait), undated
  - Chisolm, Cong. S. With Moe Biller., undated
  - Christenberry, Robert K.- NYPM (1 portrait), undated
  - Credo, Everet- Pres., NY State Federation of Post Office Clerks, AFL, undated
  - Daniels- Cong., NJ, undated
  - Darco, Al, undated
  - Delaney, Cong. J., Jul 1965
  - Devenato, Anthony, undated
  - Deutchman, Julius, undated
  - Diskin, Joe, undated
  - Di Lorenzo, John, undated
  - Ecker, Joe, undated
  - Eisenhower, D.D., 1969
  - Elardo, J., undated
  - Ergas, Leon, undated
  - Ettinger, Elsie, undated
  - Evans, Ben, Aug 1969
  - Farbstein, Cong. Leonard, Dec 1959
  - Filbey, F.- National President, APWU, undated
  - Fitzgerald, P., undated
  - Flanagan, Ted- Pres. NJ POC, Apr 1959
  - Goodman, Sid, undated
  - Gottieb, Otto- Pres Local 10, National Federation of Post Office Clerks, undated
  - Granahan- Cong., Nov 1961
  - Greco, D., Mar 1969
  - Greene, V., Mar 1964
  - Grossman, Zoltan, undated
  - Hallbeck, Roy- National Pres., National Federation of Post Office Clerks, undated
  - Hantman, S., Feb 1960
  - Harris, Lou- Claims Rep, APWU Hosp Plan
  - Henderson, W., Mar 1960
  - Johnson, Ray, 1959
  - Kanner, Moe- Sec. NY Metro, undated
  - Kantor, H.- Penn Term, undated
  - Kantor, Irene, undated
  - Karp, W., undated
  - Karth, Rep. J., undated
  - Keating, Sen. Ken, undated
  - Keating, Sean- Reg. Dir., undated
  - Keil, Julius, undated
  - Kennedy, John F. Bust., undated
  - Keogh, Rep. E., undated
  - King, Alan, undated
  - Kohn, Sidney, Feb 1960
  - Leibowitz, Al (or Joe Spitesi), undated
  - Lewis, John L.- Pres. CIO, undated
  - Lindsay, Cong. John V., undated
  - Lunenfeld, Norman, undated
  - Mckay, John- Pres. NPU, undated
  - Martine, Sal, undated
  - Magnuson, Sen W.G., undated
  - Marshall, Walter- NFPOMUE and APWU Motor Vehicle Division Leader, undated
  - Martin, J.- Rep., Mass., undated
  - Mason, C., undated
  - Meany, George- Pres. AFL, undated
  - Miller, Irving J., Nov 1959
  - Morrison, Cong. J.H., undated
  - Mosely, William- MVO Pres., undated
  - Murphy, James- Pres. Boston, Mass NPU, undated
  - Newberger- Sen., undated
  - Nix, Rep. Rob, undated
  - Nixon, R.C., undated
  - Olsen, Cong. Arnold, undated
  - Petre, Theodore A., undated
  - Reese, H.- VP Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union, undated
  - Resnick, R., Apr 1959
  - Roberts, Larry- L.B. broadcaster, undated
  - Rodriguez, undated
  - Romano, R.- Pres. Jamaica, undated
  - Rosenthal, Cong. Ben, undated
  - Rosner, Milt- Fin. Sec., undated
  - Ryland, Arthur, 1959
  - Sach, A., undated
  - Sainato, William, undated
  - St. John, Mar 1960
  - Salkowitz, Charles, undated
  - Sanchez, R., 1965
  - Schact, Sol (Raffle), undated
  - Schaffer, Robert- Post Master, New York City, undated
  - Schattner, J., undated
  - Schechter, L., undated
  - Schivee, J., undated
  - Schwartz, Bernie, undated
  - Seidman, M. (or Seiderman, the spelling varies), undated
  - Seligman, Phil, undated
  - Selvin, Jacob, Jan 1960
  - Schapiro, Milt- VP, undated
  - Shore, Jack, undated
  - Sivergleid, David- National Pres. NPU, undated
  - Skinner, G.W., Audubon Station, Nov 1961
  - Skolnick, Harry, undated
  - Sombrotto, V.- National Pres. NALC, undated
  - Somma, Anthony- Retirement Chairman, undated
  - Steward, N., undated
  - Stokes, Lew, Oct 1969
  - Sultan, Ray, undated
  - Sutter, Al, undated
  - Truman, Sen. Harry, undated
  - Verrino, Andy, undated
  - Wachtel, Sam, undated
  - Washington, T., undated
  - Weber, Josh (Josh Weber might have been a steward at General Post Office), undated
  - White, Joe, undated
  - Wiggins, Richard, undated
  - Wilensky, Ellen, undated
  - Williams, Arthur, undated
  - Wirtz, W.W.- Secretary of Labor, undated
  - Portraits-Individuals-Unidentified, undated
  - Cesar Chavez- Dir. VFWPOC, undated
- Series II: Group Portraits with Union Officials (Box 1)
  - Addabbo (Cong.), undated
  - Anfuso (Cong.) w/ B. Sufian, undated
  - Anfuso (Cong.) w/ J. Javits, undated
  - Belen- Asst. Post Master General, 1969
  - Biller, Moe, etc., undated
  - Biller w/ Daniels, 1968
  - Biller w/ Post reporter. Biller w/ Petri and Kofsky., undated
  - Biller, Moe. Story New York Post., undated
  - Biller, Moe w/ Odhuno, R., Kenya, 1967
  - Bingham (Cong.), M. Biller, B. Sufian. Leg. Rally, Jul 1965
  - Bosch (Cong.), undated
  - Bragalini, George (Postmaster), undated
  - Meeting w/ Post Master Christenberry, 1957
  - Cohen, L. w/ Manhattan and Bronx Postmasters, undated
  - Post Master General J. Edward Day w/ National officers [see also Series 2-A: Folder 34 Pres. J. F. Kennedy pay increase}, undated
  - Dempsey, Jack, 1963
  - Doherty- National Pres. NALC w/ Biller, Klein, Leo George and others, undated
  - Dollinger, I. (Cong.), 1959
  - Dulski (Cong.), undated
  - Ecker, J., undated
  - Fino (Cong.), undated
  - Flam, N. and Resnick, E. (Raffle), undated
  - Flanagan, Ted ( Jersey State Pres.), 1965
  - Fowler, Rock, Vaccaro, 1969
  - Gay, Richard w/ Schwartz, Bernard, undated
  - Goodman, S., 1967
  - Gronowski, J.A. (Post Master General), undated
  - Hahn (Reg. Dir.), undated
  - Hallbeck, Roy (Leg. Dir. National Federation of Post Office Clerks) w/ F. Grippo (Pres. Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union), undated
  - Healy (Cong.), undated
  - Jennings, Dave, undated
  - Johnston, Sen. Olin, undated
  - Kamish, H. w/ Robert Kennedy and Moe Biller, Jul 1965
  - Kapenstein, I. w/ Moe Biller, undated
  - Karp, W. w/ J. Oriel (Steward), undated
  - Keating (Sen.), undated
  - Kennedy, J.F.(Pres.). Pay Increase., undated
  - Kennedy, J.F. (Sen.), Apr 1959
  - Kennedy, Robert w/ Moe Biller, undated
  - Kennedy, R. (Sen.), NPU Convention, 1966
  - Kennedy, T. (Sen.) W/ McKay and Biller, undated
  - Kuchel, Sen. Pay Raise., 1960
  - Lefkowitz (Atty. Gen.), Aug 1961
  - Lefkowitz, Dr. M., Apr 1964
  - Meeting with A. Levitt, NY State Controller, undated
  - Lindsay, John, undated
  - Macy, John, undated
  - McCarthy, E. (Sen.), undated
  - McCormick, John, undated
  - McKay, John, undated
  - McKay, Biller, Lepper, Silvergleid, Apr 1959
  - McKay, Silvergleid (NPU National Officers), undated
  - Medli, John (Pres. NYS), undated
  - Miller, W. (Rep. Natl Chairman), undated
  - Multer (Cong.), undated
  - Murphy, Richard J. (Asst. Post Master General), NPU Ex. Board. W/ S. Goodman, M. Biller, and Silvergleib. Washington, D.C., Oct 12, 1961
  - Noreen, Walter O. St. Paul, Minn., Apr 1959
  - Powell (Cong.), Jun 23, 1965
  - Meeting with Walter Reuther. Washington, D.C., undated
  - Rockefeller (Gov.) [see also Series 11: Folder 13 Lincoln Day Dinner-1963"], May-63
  - Romney, Gov. George w/ S. Goodman, undated
  - Ryland, A., undated
  - Salkowitz, Charles w/ Prof. J. Rosenberg. Cornell University., undated
  - Saunders, I., 1969
  - Schaffer, Robert (Post Master NY), undated
  - Schwartz, Bernie, undated
  - Shapiro, S., undated
  - Silvergleid, David, undated
  - Straham (Post Master), Biller, Kantor, NYTT Delegates. New York Truck Terminal clean-up., undated
  - Sufian, B., undated
  - Teller (Cong.), Apr 1959
  - Udall (Cong.) w/ Bernie Schwartz, 1975
  - Vaccarro, N., undated
  - Vasquez, Caesar A., May 1960
  - Wagner, Robert F. (Mayor), 1961
  - Washington, Al, undated
  - Weisel, Ed (National Democratic Committeeman), undated
  - Zelenko (Cong.), J. Elardo, B. Schwartz, 1967
- Series III: Congressional Visits (Box 1)
  - Visit to Cong B Barry (3/1962), Mar 1962
  - Cong T Dulski, undated
  - Cong Halpern Leg Trip to Washington, DC (7/1961), Jul-61
  - Sen Keating, undated
  - Sen Kennedy with Biller on Senate Steps-1967
  - Sen H Lehman, undated
  - Meeting with Cong Lindsay, undated
  - Cong GM Rhodes, undated
  - B Schwartz, undated
  - B Schwartz, undated
  - Congress Visits, undated
  - Dues Checkoff Bills Introduced, undated
  - Washington Leg Trip (1/1958 and 3/1958)
  - Senate Hearing (1966)
- Series IV: Meetings (Box 1)
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Post Master New York meeting- 1955, 1956 Christmas meeting
  - Dues Increase meeting, Local 10- 6/1957
  - Telecast- 1957
  - M Biller Hospital Plan Directors- Oct 1957/ 59/ 60, 1957-1960
  - Credit Union Meeting, Local 10, NPOC- 1958
  - Convention Report- 9/ 1958, Sep 1958
  - General Post Office Inc meeting- 3/1959, Mar 1959
  - P/M Christmas O/T- 1959
  - Sid Goodman, Hicksville, Long Island, NY- 1959
  - Vote New Union, PUMBC- 1959
  - Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union meeting- 11/1959, Nov 1959
  - Meeting- 11/1959, Nov 1959
  - Formation of NPU- 1959
  - NY Metro Area PU- 10/1960, Oct 1960
  - Sub-meetings- 5/1959, 2/1960, 3/1960, Mar 1959-Mar 1960
  - M-V meeting- 7/23/1961, Jul 23, 1961
  - Executive Board Hospital Plan- 9/1961, Sep 1961
  - Task Force Hearings- 10/1961 (or 9/19/1961), Oct 1961
  - Annual Credit Union meeting- 1961
  - Annual Credit Union meeting- 1/1962, Jan 1962
  - Amendment meeting- 1963
  - Negotiating Sessions (General Post Office)- 4 to 5/1963, Apr 1963-May 1963
  - Turkey meeting- 11/1963, Nov 1963
  - Christmas meeting, Bronx- 1963, May 1963
  - A Young meeting- 1968
  - Meeting at the Shoreham Hotel- 6/24-26/1968, Jun 24, 1968 - Jun 26, 1968
  - Thanksgiving meeting- 1968
  - Meeting interviews- 11/1968, Nov 1968
  - Christmas meeting, NYPO- 1968, 1969
  - Christmas meeting, BxPO- 1968, 1969
  - Constitutional Amendment meeting- 1969
  - FDR Station L/M meeting- 3/1969, Mar 1969
  - Press Conference- 5/1969, May 1969
  - Meeting- 11/1969, Nov 1969
  - Bella Abzug- 1/1970, Jan 1970
  - Cong (NY) meeting- 1970
  - Bronx PO meeting, L Cohen Post Master, undated
  - GC Area meeting, undated
  - Harold Faggan, undated
  - Health Insurance, undated
  - Joint Conference, Local 10, etc Miscellaneous Photos, undated
  - Leg Meeting with Cong William Ryan, NY, undated
  - L/M meeting Manhattan and Bronx PO, undated
  - Maintenance, Z Grossman, undated
  - Joint meeting- MB and BR 36, undated
  - NPU, undated
  - New York Post Office meeting- Post Master M/B meeting, undated
  - Post Master meeting, undated
  - Union meeting, undated
- Series V: Stewards, B (Box 2)
  Most of the captions for the photographs include the postal station where the steward worked.
  - Bravdes, A. (3/1960), Mar 1960
  - Brennan, J.J., undated
  - Bynum, V. (Raffle), undated
  - Calgnile, Dom, undated
  - Cohen, Arnold, undated
  - Connor, W., undated
  - Ford, Louise, undated
  - Horowitz, Simon, undated
  - Rosenberg, Joe, undated
  - Seiler, Isidore, undated
  - Venable, R. (1969)
  - Zakin, Larry, undated
- Series VI: Group Portraits of Union Officials at Events (Box 2)
  - AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C. - Biller, Meany, Lane Kirkland, Josie McMillan, 1980
  - Al Darco and NY Metro Officers signing 1187's, undated
  - Eastern Regional Conference, Asbury Park, Jan 16, 1953 - Jan 18, 1953
  - Housewarming, Washington, D.C., 1968
  - M-H Merger Locals #1 and 203, undated
  - M-V Employees (8/1961) [1 picture w/ John Nicholas, Ted Flanagan, Duke Moore, William Mosely, Biller, Goodman, Edward Jones], undated
  - National Postal Transport (11/1959) [Biller, Shapiro, Goodman, Schwartz], undated
  - NY Fed. M. Rosner, H. Goldberg, A., undated
  - PO: Sub-committee on Reclassification, undated
  - PUMB- Pre-elect Biller and Pres, Mar 1959
  - Reg. Dir. Coonen, SL Investigation at Church St. Station, 1960
  - Retirees: Morris, A. Somma, J. White, J. Friedman, undated
  - Testimonial Dinner, circa 1967
  - Thanksgiving, miscellaneous pictures [Misc. Pictures, 1960; Cong. L. Faber visits, Ladies Auxiliary; office staff]
  - Washington, D.C. Joint Conference, Jan 1958
  - Washington, D.C. Trip, 1957
- Series VII: House/Senate Members Visit the Union (Box 2)
  - Cong F Brasco, undated
  - Cong E Celler, F Handman, Pres, undated
  - Cong T Dulski, undated
  - Cong Paul Fino, undated
  - Cong Jacob Gilbert Leg meeting (12/1960), Dec 1960
  - Sen JK Javits w/ Goodman and Biller (12/1959-1/1960), Dec 1959-Jan 1960
  - Sen Kennedy at regular members meeting (9/20/67), Sep 20, 1967
  - Sen McCormick Installation of officers, Metro and Branch 36 leaders, undated
  - Cong Powell, undated
  - Cong AE Santangello (1959)
  - Cong Teller (12/1959), Dec 1959
  - Cong M Udall, undated
  - Congressional visits 1969
- Series VIII: Membership Meetings (Box 2)
  - Regular members meeting- 11/1957, Nov 1957
  - Regular meeting- 1958
  - Members meeting- 11/1958, Nov 1958
  - Membership meeting- 12/14/1958, Dec 14, 1958
  - Members meeting- 6/1959, Jun 1959
  - Members meeting- 10/1959, Oct 1959
  - Members meeting- 1/20/1960 (or 11/21/59), Jan 20, 1960
  - Members speak- 2/17/1960, Feb 17, 1960
  - Members meeting Dues Increase- 1/18/1961, Jan 18, 1961
- Series IX: Delegates, C (Box 2)
  - Applenhaite, G. (Or Applewhaite), undated
  - Corbusieri, D., undated
  - Dolinko, K., undated
  - Easley, G., 1969
  - Hankin, I., undated
  - Iulo, L., undated
  - Kilpatrick, J., undated
  - Levy, Ben, Aug 1961
  - Lipschitz, Abe, undated
  - Nunez, F., undated
  - Oriel, J., undated
  - Pumerantz, Miltz, undated
  - Ramirez, Dave, undated
  - Rosenberg, I., undated
  - Ross, Harry, undated
  - Zimmerman, Carl, undated
- Series X: Installation of Officers (Box 2)
  - Installation of Officers, Apr 5, 1957
  - Installation of Officers, Apr 3, 1959
  - Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union Installation, 1962
  - Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union Installation, 1963
  - Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union Installation, 1966
  - Buffalo Installation, 1968
  - Installation of Officers Local 10, National Federation of Post Office Clerks, undated
  - National Postal Union, Installation of Officers, undated
- Series XI: Conventions/Conferences, D (Box 2)
  - Chicago Convention- 1956
  - NY State AFL Convention, Buffalo, NY- 1957
  - Detroit Progressives Conference- 1957
  - Eastern Progressive Conference- 9/29/1957, Sep 29, 1957
  - Progressive Conference- 11/1958, Nov 1958
  - National Federation of Post Office Clerks National Convention, Boston, Mass- 1958
  - NPU Conference, Washington, DC- 1/16-17/1959, Jan 16, 1959 - Jan 17, 1959
  - New York State Convention- Late 1950's (?), 1955-1959
  - State Convention and Washington, DC Convention- 1961
  - New York State Convention, Mt Vernon- 8/6/1961, Aug 6, 1961
  - First Annual Convention, NY State NPU, Long Beach, Long Island- 5/1962, May 1962
  - NPU Convention, Long Beach, Long Island- 1962
  - National Convention- 1966
  - National Convention- 1966
  - Merger Convention- 2/1966, Feb 1966
  - Officers and Delegates to National NPU Convention- 1968
  - NPU National Convention, Puerto Rico- 1968
  - NY Conference- 5/ 1969 Schwartz, Ecker, Silvergleid, Shapiro, May 1969
  - National Convention, St Paul, Minn, undated
  - National Convention- 1974
  - NPU National Convention, undated
  - Convention, New Orleans, undated
  - New York State Convention, NPU, undated
- Series XII: Boards/Committees/Councils, V (Box 2)
  - MB Advise Conditions- Reg Eng Meeting- 6/1958, Jun 1958
  - Board Officers meeting w/ Council- 6/12/59 (or 1/1959), Jun 12, 1959
  - Credit Union Officers- 1959
  - Credit Union Directors meeting, Executive Board meeting- 1/11/1960, Jan 11, 1960
  - M Biller Task Force- 9/1961, Sep 1961
  - Postal Council- 2/1962, Feb 1962
  - Metro Postal Council- 1/1962, Jan 1962
  - Metro Postal Council- 1965
  - Mail Handlers Council (National)- 6/1969, Jun 1969
  - Board of Officers- 1970
  - NPU National Automation Committee at Washington, DC- 5/1965, May 1965
  - NPU National Automation Committee, Detroit Michigan, undated
  - National Executive Board- 1958-1961
  - National Board, Washington, DC- 1960
  - Metro Area Bargaining Council petitions NLRB second region for certification election, undated
  - Executive Board, NPU, undated
- Series XIII: Women's Auxiliary, VI (Box 2)
  - Ladies' Auxiliary, Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union N Frankfort, undated
  - Women's Auxiliary Installation- 1961
  - Women's Auxiliary Installation- 4/1963, Apr 1963
  - Women's Auxiliary- 1963
  - Women's Auxiliary luncheon for N Franfort- 1963
  - Ladies' Auxiliary- 1965
  - Annual Installation of Officers, Ladies' Auxiliary, Local 10, National Federation of Post Office Clerks, undated
- Series XIV: Demonstrations/Rallies, VII (Box 2)
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 1957
  - Pay Raise Rally, Central Commercial HS- 3/24/1957, Mar 24, 1957
  - Pay Raise Postcard to President-1959
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 3/1960, Mar 1960
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 6/1961, Jun 1961
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 8/1961, Aug 1961
  - Legislative Rally- 3/1962, May 1962
  - Washington Pay Rally- 11/ 6-7/1962, Nov 6, 1962 - Nov 7, 1962
  - Washington Pay Rally- 11/6-7/1962, Nov 6, 1962 - Nov 7, 1962
  - WMS Rally, New York and Washington, DC- 1963
  - Rally- 1963
  - Rally- 5/1963, May-63
  - Freedom March- 8/28/1963, Aug 28, 1963
  - Pay Demo- 3/1964, May-64
  - Demo Met Area Council- 1965
  - Anti-POMSIP Rally- 1966
  - Pay rally station demo- 1967 [peanut campaign]
  - Rockefeller Center Station demo- 1967
  - Poor Peoples March- 1968
  - Democratic Party Rally- 4/19/69, Apr 19, 1968
  - Washington Rally- 1969
  - Peanuts Legislative Program- 1969
  - Legislative Rally (Pay Raise)- 1969
  - Pay Raise Rally, Washington, DC- 5/1969 [peanut campaign], May 1969
  - ACRMD Kids- 5/1969, May 1969